http://www.tuscaroras.com/index.php/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Main MenuHomeWebmailPrivacy PolicyHelp Support This SiteAmazon Direct LinkClick Here to see how to help support this site at no cost to youNative American Video ClipsChildren's Video ClipsVideo Clips About the IroquoisStories and LegendsChief Oren Lyons Video ClipsEnvironmental InformationWaste Management in Indian CountryHaudenosaunee Environmental
Task ForceTuscarora EnvironmentMuseum InformationMohawk ChapelNative North American Travelling CollegeSix Nations Indian MuseumSeneca Iroquois National MuseumIroquois Indian MuseumThe Woodland Cultural CentreWeb Sites at TcomMe & U - Mother Earth & UsJohn Wigle's HomepageHaudenosaunee Children's PageHaudenosaunee Paper Dolls
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Tuscarora & Six Nations Websites collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://tuscaroras.com/ website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Tuscarora & Six Nations Websites. Personal identification information We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. Non-personal identification information We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. Web browser cookies Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. How we use collected information Tuscarora & Six Nations Websites may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes: - To improve our Site We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. - To send periodic emails We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. How we protect your information We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Sharing your personal information We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. Third party websites Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. Advertising Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Changes to this privacy policy Tuscarora & Six Nations Websites has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. Your acceptance of these terms By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. Contacting us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: Tuscarora & Six Nations Websites http://tuscaroras.com/ 34 Spruce Ln Indiana PA 15701 724-349-3103 This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. This document was last updated on June 06, 2012 Privacy policy created by http://www.generateprivacypolicy.com
Search ...
Tuscarora InformationTuscarora Audio ClipsTuscarora Historical Timeline1890 Tuscarora Nation MapThe Tuscarora LanguageThe People V Neil Patterson Jr.Fed. Power Comm. vs Tuscarora Nation257 F2d 885 Tuscarora Nation of Indians v. Power Authority of State of New York WChief Elias Johnson Suspended1711 The Tuscarora War1891 - Legends, Traditions, and Laws of the Iroquois, or Six Nations, and History of the Tuscarora IndiansTraditional Indian Corn Soup RecipeTuscarora New Year FestivalTuscarora Christmas 1937Tuscaroras in the Civil WarTuscarora's Influence on PennsylvaniaIroquois InformationHaudenosaunee Views in the Late Nineteenth CenturyAbout the Iroquois ConstitutionIroquois ConstitutionIroquois Article at Wikipedia1892 David Cusick's Six NationsThe Six Nations Confederacy During the American RevolutionThe Oneida Nation in the American RevolutionTreaty Information1784 Treaty with Six Nations1789 Deed From The Six Nations of Indians to the State of Pennsylvania1789 Articles of Agreement Between Six Nations and Pennsylvania1789 Treaty with Six Nations1792 Articles of Agreement (Five Nations)1794 Treaty of Canandaigua1794 Treaty With The Tuscarora, Oneida and Stockbridge Indians1796 Jay Treaty of Amity Commerce and Navigation1796 Treaty with the Seven Nations of Canada1797 Treaty with the Mohawk1797 Treaty with the Senecas1797 Treaty Of Big Tree1803 Treaty with the Tuscarora Nation1838 Treaty at Buffalo Creek
Note: Tuscaroras.com is not affiliated with or approved or endorsed by the Tuscarora Nation of New York.
While there are official websites for various organizations, Tuscaroras.com is not the official website of the Tuscarora Nation of New York. Views expressed on the individual websites hosted here are those of the administrator of each individual website. Tuscaroras.com does not have access to tribal records or genealogical information of any kind.
©1996 - 2019 Tuscarora and Six Nations Websites
All Rights Reserved
Joomla template created with Artisteer.
